

PERSONAL PROFILE

A conscientious & professional person who has invaluable experience and passionate in Financial reporting & analysis as a Management Accountant with proven ability to work under pressure within time constraints. Friendly and approachable with an eager-to-learn mindset.

EDUCATION

- University of Economics and Law-Bachelor in Auditing, 2017
- Certificate in Finance Accounting & Business -ICAEW, 2019
- SQL & Power BI-Essential learning-Linkedin, 2020
- TOEIC 955/990-2017

CONTACT INFO

- District 3 HCM City Vietnam
- vidoannguyentuong@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/vidoannguyentuong
- 0932128680

SKILLS

- Advance Microsoft Excel
- Proficient knowledge and experience in SQL, Data Studio & Power BI
- · Strong critical & logical thinking
- Diligent & attentive to detail
- Versatile & result-oriented in a fast pace environment
- Fast learner & able to work under high pressure
- Successful working in a team environment and independently

WORK EXPERIENCE

KPMG, Senior auditor

OCT 2018 - NOV 2020

- Couch & coordinate the team during the fieldwork at client
- Conduct audit procedures including test of control design & implementation and perform substantive test of details for companies in FMCG, Trading, Agents and Banking fields
- Analyze data for further financial analysis (especially items effect the the Bottom lines, Loan portfolio of Bank) accompany with applying knowledge of industry to identify risk areas, reasons for the abnormal fluctuations & provide information for Financial reports disclosure
- Conduct audit procedures including test of control design & implementation and perform substantive test of details for companies in FMCG, Trading, Agents and Banking fields
- Propose audit findings & solutions (average 3 findings/ client)

DIHK International Service, Accountant

SEP 2017 - SEP 2018

- · Process bank transactions weekly & perform book-keeping
- Support Finance Manager in other financial reports-cash budgeting, asset management.
- Check & reconcile reports from outsourcing VAS accountant with internal system's reports
- Monitored ongoing projects of sales team for VAT issuance
- Reduce time of monthly account reconcile from 7 to 3 days
- Sucessfully support FM in Capital-injection from Parent's co.



LANGUAGE

• English: Advance

• Vietnames: Native

REFERENCE

Ms. Hien Duong -Finance Manager From German Industry and Commerce Vietnam (DIHK)

Email: hien.duong@vietnam.ahk.de Phone: +84 (28) 3823 9083

Ms. Uyen Pham -Audit Assistant Manager From *KPMG Vietnam*

Email: upham@kpmg.com.vn Phone: +84 366665341

WORK EXPERIENCE

Prudential Vietnam, AML (short-term contract)

APR 2017 - AUG 2017

- Scan, document & report Anti-money laundering check on suspicious cases or high value contract to higher level (100 cases/ day)
- Complete assessment report of suspicious and high-risk customers (4 reports/month)

PwC (PricewaterhouseCoopers), Audit intern

DEC 2016 - MAR 2017

- Support Senior Auditor in analyzing data, data processing, format financial reports
- Performance auditing procedures for non-significant sections and support senior teammates in investing documents'